<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pagi Maula</title>
    
    
    
    <link>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pagi Maula</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:04:37 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All of it</title>
      <link>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/all-of-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:04:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/all-of-it/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
           ALl of it # 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another blog post</title>
      <link>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/another-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:04:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/another-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          There wasn&amp;rsquo;t a whole lot more that could be done. It had become a wait-and-see situation with the final results no longer in her control. That didn&amp;rsquo;t stop her from trying to control the situation. She demanded that things be done as she desperately tried to control what couldn&amp;rsquo;t be.
Her breath exited her mouth in big puffs as if she were smoking a cigarette. The morning dew had made her clothes damp and she shivered from the chill in the air.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In plane sight</title>
      <link>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/in-plane-sight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:04:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/in-plane-sight/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          &amp;ldquo;Begin today!&amp;rdquo; That&amp;rsquo;s all the note said. There was no indication from where it came or who may have written it. Had it been meant for someone else? Meghan looked around the room, but nobody made eye contact back. For a brief moment, she thought it might be a message for her to follow her dreams, but ultimately decided it was easier to ignore it as she crumpled it up and threw it away.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:04:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Introduction # This is bold text, and this is emphasized text.
Visit the Hugo website!
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The-efficiency-with-which-he-paired-the-socks-in-the-drawer-was-quite-admirable</title>
      <link>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/the-efficiency-with-which-he-paired-the-socks-in-the-drawer-was-quite-admirable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:04:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/the-efficiency-with-which-he-paired-the-socks-in-the-drawer-was-quite-admirable/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          The underground bunker was filled with chips and candy. It was a weird concept. Why would I really need to generate a random paragraph? Could I actually learn something from doing so? All these questions were running through her head as she pressed the generate button. To her surprise, she found what she least expected to see. The wave roared towards them with speed and violence they had not anticipated.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Underestimating is holding you back</title>
      <link>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/underestinating-is-holding-you-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:04:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/underestinating-is-holding-you-back/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          I feel like underestimating how hard something is directly contributing to commitment issues and procrastination. For example, if you are between the ages of 16 and 27 and you had a semi-deep conversation with your friend, chances are you have thought about starting a podcast. The thing is most of us haven’t even taken the first step to create an account, my friend and I decided that we would host a podcast in his car this past summer, and we never even recorded a single clip of footage.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Spent Alone</title>
      <link>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/time-spent-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 22:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pagi-maula.github.io/posts/time-spent-alone/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Good Question: Is It Bad to Spend a Lot of Time Alone? # The underground bunker was filled with chips and candy. Humans are social animals. Our well-being depends on the company of others.
The research linking loneliness to depression, cardiovascular disease, and other health problems is so conclusive that doctors now mention social isolation in the same breath as smoking and a sedentary lifestyle when discussing major public health risks.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>